Finding Aid for the Delbert Mann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Delbert Mann
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0007
42.42 linear_feet
- Productions
  - Productions Directed by Delbert Mann
    - Julius Caesar, 1947; Script (Box 1)
    - Theatre of the Mind – My Name Is Wilma, 11 August 1949; Script (Box 1)
    - Theatre of the Mind (untitled story), 18 August 1949; Script (Box 1)
    - The Mary Kay and Johnny Show, 15 September 1949; Script (Box 1)
    - The Mary Kay and Johnny Show, 22 September 1949; Script Prop List (Box 1)
    - Pengallen’s Bell, 14 November 1949; Script Cast List (Box 1)
    - Bethel Merriday, 8 January 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - The Marriages, 22 January 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Vincent Van Gogh, 5 March 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - The Trial of Steven Kent, 19 March 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Nocturne, 2 April 1950; Script (Box 1)
    - The End Is Known, 16 April 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - The Feast, 7 May 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Sense and Sensibility, 4 June 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Anything Can Happen, 18 June 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Othello, 27 August 1950; Script Cast List Correspondence (Box 1)
    - High Tor, 10 September 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - A Husband for Mama, 15 October 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - The Gambler, 29 October 1950; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - The Symbol, 7 January 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Let Them Be Seacaptains, 18 February 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Bulletin 120, 25 March 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Routine Assignment, 8 April 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Birth of The Movies, 22 April 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - A Secret Island, 6 May 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Justice and Mr. Pleznik, 20 May 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Operation Airlift, 17 June 1951; Script Cast List (Box 1)
    - Come Alive, 19 August 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - October Story, 14 October 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Flight to Freedom, 11 November 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Money to Burn, 9 December 1951; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - I Was Stalin’s Prisoner, 23 December 1951; Script Cast List Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Segment, 27 January 1952; Correspondence (Box 1)
    - The Rich Boy, 10 February 1952; Script Cast List Scene and Actor Breakdown Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Dusty Portrait, 9 March 1952; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - The Medea Cup, 13 April 1952; Script Cast List Scene and Actor Breakdown Set Sketches (Box 2)
    - The Travellers, 27 April 1952; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - The Twenty-Third Mission, 11 May 1952; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Four Meetings, 8 June 1952; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - The Five Fathers of Pepi, 10 August 1952; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Three Sundays, 24 August 1952; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Better Than Walking, 26 October 1952; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Parole Chief, 16 November 1952; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Eisenhower Presidential Campaign, October-November 1952; Scripts for Interviews, 3 November 1952 and undated. One copy signed by Eisenhower. Speech by Dwight D. Eisenhower, 30 October 1952 Notes Ticket to Eisenhower Rally at Madison Square Garden, 30 October 1952 (Box 2)
    - Search, 7 December 1952; Script Cast List Scene and Actor Breakdown Correspondence (Box 2)
    - The Reluctant Citizen, 8 February 1953; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Wings On My Feet, 22 February 1953; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - The Rumor, 8 March 1953; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Wish On the Moon, 29 March 1953; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Printer’s Measure, 26 April 1953; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - A Little Something in Reserve, 10 May 1953; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Marty, 24 May 1953; Scripts Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Catch a Falling Star, 28 June 1953; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Ernie Barger Is 50, 9 August 1953; Script Cast List Scene and Actor Breakdown Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Hollywood Tandem, 23 August 1953; Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Othello, 6 September 1953; Script Cast List Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Holiday Song, 20 September 1953; Script Cast List (Box 2)
    - The Bachelor Party, 11 October 1953; Script Cast List Scene and Actor Breakdown (Box 2)
    - The Haven, 1 November 1953; Script Cast List (Box 2)
    - Wings Over Barriers, 20 December 1953; Script Cast List Credits (Box 3)
    - The Huntress, 14 February 1954; Script Cast List Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Yale Drama School Remote, 21 February 1954; Correspondence (Box 3)
    - The Inward Horizon, 14 March 1954; Correspondence (Box 3)
    - The Mother, 4 April 1954; Script Cast List Scene and Actor Breakdown (Box 3)
    - Somebody Special, 6 June 1954; Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Middle of the Night, 19 September 1954; Script Cast List Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Marty, 1955; Publicity Reviews Program, Twenty-Eighth Academy Awards Presentation, 21 March 1956 Invitations, Russian Premier, 1959 Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Yellow Jack, 10 January 1955; Script Cast List Crew List Correspondence (Box 3)
    - The Rabbit Trap, 13 February 1955; Script Cast List (Box 3)
    - Play Me Hearts and Flowers, 6 March 1955; Sheet Music Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Darkness at Noon, 2 May 1955; Script Cast List Crew List Correspondence (Box 4)
    - The Petrified Forest, 30 May 1955; Script Cast List Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Our Town, 19 September 1955; Script Musical Breakdown Sheet Music Review Correspondence (Box 3)
    - The Answer, 4 October 1955; Correspondence (Box 3)
    - The Day Lincoln Was Shot, 11 February 1956; Scripts Cast List Correspondence Presentation on Lincoln’s Assassination in Theatre Arts (Box 3)
    - Harvard University, 25 March 1956; Script Scene and Actor Breakdown Location Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Speaking of Murder, November 1956; Reviews Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Wide, Wide World, 6 January 1957; Script; Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Lee at Gettysburg, 20 January 1957; Script; Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Desire Under the Elms, 1957; Script Cast List Screen Treatment Background Schedule Sketches Map, Paramount Pictures Publicity Correspondence (Box 5)
    - The Bachelor Party, 1957; Scripts Schedules Sketches Correspondence (Box 5)
    - The Plot to Kill Stalin, 25 September 1958; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Background Notes Scene and Actor Breakdown Schedule Judicial Opinion Correspondence (Box 6)
    - The Long March, 2 october 1958; Script; Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Separate Tables, 1958; Scripts Set Designs Essays Program, Stage Version Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Separate Tables, 1958; Scripts Set Designs Essays Program, Stage Version Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Middle of the Night, 1959; Script Schedules Set Designs Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Wuthering Heights, April-May 1959; Partial Script Libretto Cast List Notes Set Diagrams Program Correspondence (Box 7)
    - What Makes Sammy Run?, 27 September 1959, 4 October 1959; Scripts Cast List Crew List Scene and Actor Breakdown Notes Schedule Budget Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Crime, Inc., 25 October 1959; Script Cast List Crew List Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Bernstein and the Philharmonic in Venice, November 1959; Script Score (Box 8)
    - The Tunnel, 10 December 1959; Script Cast List Scene and Actor Breakdown Schedules Correspondence (Box 8)
    - The Dark at the Top of the Stairs, 1960; Credits Scene Summaries Set and Scene Breakdown Set List Set Designs Set Sketches Wardrobe Plots Map, Warner Brothers Pictures Filmstrip (fragment) Clippings Correspondence (Box 8)
    - The Outsider, 1960; Outline Scripts Notes Background Crew List Set and Scene Breakdown Scene Plans Set Designs Sketches Budget Film Seminar Material Correspondence (Box 8)
    - The Outsider, 1960; Outline Scripts Notes Background Crew List Set and Scene Breakdown Scene Plans Set Designs Sketches Budget Film Seminar Material Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Lover, Come Back, 1961; Script Crew List Sketches Budget Correspondence (Box 9)
    - That Touch of Mink, 1961; Script Notes Budget Correspondence (Box 10)
    - A Gathering of Eagles, 1962; Treatment Scripts Background Notes Scene Plans Schedules Budgets Negotiations Correspondence (Box 10)
    - A Gathering of Eagles, 1962; Treatment Scripts Background Notes Scene Plans Schedules Budgets Negotiations Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Tovarich, 1963; Scripts Sheet Music Financial Statements Publicity Programs Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Tovarich, 1963; Scripts Sheet Music Financial Statements Publicity Programs Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Dear Heart, 1963 (Released 1965); Scripts Synopsis Credits Notes Music Notes Set List Budget Review Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Quick, Before It Melts, 1964; Scripts Synopsis Script for Trailer Credits Cast and Crew Lists Notes Music Notes Scene and Footage Breakdown Set List Set Designs Location Information Legal Research Budget Publicity Preview Reports (Box 13)
    - Quick, Before It Melts, 1964; Scripts Synopsis Script for Trailer Credits Cast and Crew Lists Notes Music Notes Scene and Footage Breakdown Set List Set Designs Location Information Legal Research Budget Publicity Preview Reports (Box 14)
    - Mister Buddwing, 1966; Scripts Notes Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Scene and Footage Breakdown Music Notes Sheet Music Schedules Set List Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Production Reports Legal Research Budget Preview Reports Publicity Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Mister Buddwing, 1966; Scripts Notes Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Scene and Footage Breakdown Music Notes Sheet Music Schedules Set List Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Production Reports Legal Research Budget Preview Reports Publicity Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Mister Buddwing, 1966; Scripts Notes Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Scene and Footage Breakdown Music Notes Sheet Music Schedules Set List Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Production Reports Legal Research Budget Preview Reports Publicity Correspondence (Box 16)
    - Fitzwilly, 1966; Scripts Script for Trailer Cast Lists Casting Photographs Credits Notes Scene Breakdown Production Shots List Music Schedules Set List Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Research Correspondence (Box 16)
    - Fitzwilly, 1966; Scripts Script for Trailer Cast Lists Casting Photographs Credits Notes Scene Breakdown Production Shots List Music Schedules Set List Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Research Correspondence (Box 17)
    - The Pink Jungle, 1967; Scripts Notes Music Notes Scene and Footage Breakdown List of Scenes to be Looped Continuity Breakdown Schedules Production Reports Set Lists Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Correspondence (Box 18)
    - Heidi, 17 November 1968; Outline Scripts Synopsis Cast Lists Casting Photographs Credits Notes Scene List Scene and Timing Breakdown List of Lines to be Looped Production Shots List Music Schedules Sketches Location Photographs Budget Publicity Correspondence (Box 19)
    - Heidi, 17 November 1968; Outline Scripts Synopsis Cast Lists Casting Photographs Credits Notes Scene List Scene and Timing Breakdown List of Lines to be Looped Production Shots List Music Schedules Sketches Location Photographs Budget Publicity Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Saturday Adoption, 4 December 1968; Scripts Synopsis Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown List of Selected Takes Prop Lists Program Format Schedules Set Design Budget Legal Research Publicity Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Saturday Adoption, 4 December 1968; Scripts Synopsis Cast Lists Crew Lists Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown List of Selected Takes Prop Lists Program Format Schedules Set Design Budget Legal Research Publicity Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Zelda, March 1969; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Notes Production Analysis Prop List Schedules Program Publicity Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Zelda, March 1969; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Notes Production Analysis Prop List Schedules Program Publicity Correspondence (Box 22)
    - David Copperfield, 15 March 1970; Treatment/Outline Scripts Narration Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew Lists Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Illustrations Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans List of Scenes to be Looped Lists of Suggested Cuts and Additions Effects List Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Rushes Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Documents Legal Research Publicity Reviews Correspondence (Box 22)
    - David Copperfield, 15 March 1970; Treatment/Outline Scripts Narration Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew Lists Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Illustrations Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans List of Scenes to be Looped Lists of Suggested Cuts and Additions Effects List Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Rushes Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Documents Legal Research Publicity Reviews Correspondence (Box 23)
    - David Copperfield, 15 March 1970; Treatment/Outline Scripts Narration Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew Lists Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Illustrations Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans List of Scenes to be Looped Lists of Suggested Cuts and Additions Effects List Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Rushes Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Documents Legal Research Publicity Reviews Correspondence (Box 24)
    - David Copperfield, 15 March 1970; Treatment/Outline Scripts Narration Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew Lists Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Illustrations Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans List of Scenes to be Looped Lists of Suggested Cuts and Additions Effects List Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Rushes Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Documents Legal Research Publicity Reviews Correspondence (Box 25)
    - Jane Eyre, 24 March 1971; Outlines Scripts Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew List Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Scene Plans List of Suggested Cuts Prop Lists Program Format Sheet Music Schedules Production Plans Daily Progress Reports Rushes Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Documents Publicity Correspondence (Box 26)
    - Jane Eyre, 24 March 1971; Outlines Scripts Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew List Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Scene Plans List of Suggested Cuts Prop Lists Program Format Sheet Music Schedules Production Plans Daily Progress Reports Rushes Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Documents Publicity Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Jane Eyre, 24 March 1971; Outlines Scripts Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew List Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Scene Plans List of Suggested Cuts Prop Lists Program Format Sheet Music Schedules Production Plans Daily Progress Reports Rushes Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Designs Sketches Location Information Location Photographs Budget Legal Documents Publicity Correspondence (Box 28)
    - Kidnapped, 1971; Outlines Scripts Narration and Introduction Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene Summaries Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans Production Plans Production Shots List Reel List Lists of Suggested Cuts and Additions Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Lists Extras and Animals List Wardrobe Lists Prop Lists Camera Equipment List Sketches Location Information Budget Legal Research Publicity Reviews Correspondence (Box 28)
    - Kidnapped, 1971; Outlines Scripts Narration and Introduction Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene Summaries Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans Production Plans Production Shots List Reel List Lists of Suggested Cuts and Additions Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Lists Extras and Animals List Wardrobe Lists Prop Lists Camera Equipment List Sketches Location Information Budget Legal Research Publicity Reviews Correspondence (Box 29)
    - Kidnapped, 1971; Outlines Scripts Narration and Introduction Cast Lists Casting Photographs Crew List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene Summaries Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans Production Plans Production Shots List Reel List Lists of Suggested Cuts and Additions Program Format Schedules Daily Progress Reports Daily Diary Continuity Sheets Set Lists Extras and Animals List Wardrobe Lists Prop Lists Camera Equipment List Sketches Location Information Budget Legal Research Publicity Reviews Correspondence (Box 30)
    - She Waits, 28 January 1972; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Program Format Schedules Set Designs Wardrobe List Daily Production Reports Daily Diary Budget Legal Research Contract Summaries Ratings Report Correspondence (Box 30)
    - She Waits, 28 January 1972; Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Titles and Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Program Format Schedules Set Designs Wardrobe List Daily Production Reports Daily Diary Budget Legal Research Contract Summaries Ratings Report Correspondence (Box 31)
    - Ben Franklin, 1972 (never aired), Scripts Cast Lists Crew List Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Editing Notes and Show Rundown Program Format List of Suggested cuts Schedules Sketches Location Information Legal Research Publicity Correspondence (Box 31)
    - Ben Franklin, 1972 (never aired), Scripts Cast Lists Crew List Credits Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Background Scene and Timing Breakdown Editing Notes and Show Rundown Program Format List of Suggested cuts Schedules Sketches Location Information Legal Research Publicity Correspondence (Box 32)
    - No Place to Run, 1972; Script (Partial) Cast Lists Crew List Notes Schedules Production Reports Script Supervisor’s Reports Daily Editorial Reports Set List Location Information Location Photographs (Box 32)
    - The Man Without a Country, 24 April 1973; Script Report Scripts with Script Notes Character Descriptions Cast Lists Crew List Credits and Titles Contact List Notes Music Notes Background Filming Plans Production Plans Sound Effects List Program Format Schedules Daily Production Reports Location Information Publicity Standards and Practices Script Reviews Reviews Correspondence (Box 32)
    - The Man Without a Country, 24 April 1973; Script Report Scripts with Script Notes Character Descriptions Cast Lists Crew List Credits and Titles Contact List Notes Music Notes Background Filming Plans Production Plans Sound Effects List Program Format Schedules Daily Production Reports Location Information Publicity Standards and Practices Script Reviews Reviews Correspondence (Box 33)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1 February 1973; Cast and Crew Lists Music Cues Sound Cues Publicity Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Joie, 12 December 1973; Scripts Cast List Credits Notes Music Notes Scene and Actor Breakdown Schedules Daily Production Reports Script Supervisor’s Daily Reports Location Information Legal Research Broadcast Standards Script Reviews Correspondence (Box 33)
    - The First Woman President, 14 April 1974; Scripts Cast Lists Script Distribution List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Lighting Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Prop Lists Filming Plans Program Format Schedules Set Design Program Practices Script Reviews Ratings Report Correspondence (Box 33)
    - The First Woman President, 14 April 1974; Scripts Cast Lists Script Distribution List Notes Music Notes Sound Notes Lighting Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Prop Lists Filming Plans Program Format Schedules Set Design Program Practices Script Reviews Ratings Report Correspondence (Box 34)
    - Your Place or Mine, 1974; Scripts Cast and Crew List Notes Sound Effects Notes Prop Notes Wardrobe Notes Schedule (Box 34)
    - Birch Interval, 1974 (Released 1976); Script Report Scripts Script Revisions Cast Lists Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans First Cut Continuity One Line Continuity Traveling Shots List Wild Lines and Additional Dialogue Daily Production Requirements Lists Day Players List Schedules Daily Production Reports Set Lists Set Designs Sketches Prop Lists Location Information Publicity Notices Correspondence (Box 35)
    - Birch Interval, 1974 (Released 1976); Script Report Scripts Script Revisions Cast Lists Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans First Cut Continuity One Line Continuity Traveling Shots List Wild Lines and Additional Dialogue Daily Production Requirements Lists Day Players List Schedules Daily Production Reports Set Lists Set Designs Sketches Prop Lists Location Information Publicity Notices Correspondence (Box 36)
    - Birch Interval, 1974 (Released 1976); Script Report Scripts Script Revisions Cast Lists Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans First Cut Continuity One Line Continuity Traveling Shots List Wild Lines and Additional Dialogue Daily Production Requirements Lists Day Players List Schedules Daily Production Reports Set Lists Set Designs Sketches Prop Lists Location Information Publicity Notices Correspondence (Box 37)
    - Birch Interval, 1974 (Released 1976); Script Report Scripts Script Revisions Cast Lists Notes Music Notes Scene and Timing Breakdown Filming Plans First Cut Continuity One Line Continuity Traveling Shots List Wild Lines and Additional Dialogue Daily Production Requirements Lists Day Players List Schedules Daily Production Reports Set Lists Set Designs Sketches Prop Lists Location Information Publicity Notices Correspondence (Box 38)
    - The Legendary Curse of the Hope Diamond, 27 March 1975; Outline Scripts Cast Lists Crew Lists Notes Music Notes Background Scene Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Sound Effects List Program Format Schedules Production Plans Production Requirements List Technical Report Set Design Prop Lists Wardrobe List Budget Publicity Program Practices Reviews Correspondence (Box 38)
    - Francis Gary Powers: The True Story of the U-2 Incident, 1976; Script Report Scripts Cast Lists Notes Background Character Descriptions Scene and Timing Breakdown Continuity Notes Program Format Schedules Daily Production Reports Set List Set Design Location Information Location Photographs Broadcast Standards Review Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Breaking Up, 1976 (Released 2 January 1978); Scripts Character List Cast Lists Titles Crew Lists Notes Music Notes Scene Lists Dialogue Post Sync Sound Effects List Schedules Production Plans Daily Production Reports Daily Reports Set Lists Location and Set Breakdown Wardrobe List Location Information Contact Lists Budget Broadcast Standards and Practices Reviews Publicity Correspondence (Box 39)